<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<SoccEval1.1>
<TEXT><![CDATA[http://www.theguardian.com/football/2015/feb/10/liverpool-tottenham-hotspur-premier-league-match-report

Liverpool 3-2 Tottenham Hotspur | Premier League match report


Mario Balotelli peeled off his gloves on the final whistle, ignored the jubilant Liverpool celebrations in the far corner of the pitch and headed straight down the tunnel as Colin Pascoe offered an embrace. No joy, no show of relief, not even a glimmer of satisfaction. Perhaps he simply forgot what a matchwinner is supposed to do.
 
Balotelli produced his first Premier League goal in 13 appearances for Liverpool to seal a crucial late victory over Tottenham Hotspur, one that puts Brendan Rodgers’ side firmly in the hunt for Champions League qualification and stalled the momentum of their enterprising visitors.
 
There were seven minutes remaining when a fellow substitute, Adam Lallana, drove an inviting cross behind Jan Vertonghen and Balotelli ghosted in to convert beyond Hugo Lloris. Liverpool’s principal owner, John W Henry, and chairman Tom Werner were looking on from the Main Stand and the looming draw would have done little for their club’s top-four prospects. The Italy international has toiled badly since his £16m move from Milan but the late winner showed his sense of occasion remains intact.
 
“I’m sure he’ll be smiling in the dressing room because he’s just won us the game,” offered Jordan Henderson, and Balotelli would later post a beaming photo of himself on Instagram. “He’s immensely happy,” claimed Pascoe, Liverpool’s assistant manager who took over post-match media duties with Rodgers catching a flight to Europe for club business.
 
Rodgers had spoken ominously on the eve of Spurs’ visit about what failure to take maximum points would mean for the remainder of Liverpool’s season. Raheem Sterling was sidelined with a foot injury suffered in the FA Cup replay at Bolton Wanderers, Lucas Leiva for the next four to six weeks with a thigh problem, and Spurs arrived buoyed by the derby win over Arsenal and with the confidence generated by only one defeat in 10 league games.
       
But Daniel Sturridge returned for his first league start since Liverpool’s 3-0 win at White Hart Lane in August and would influence another defeat for Mauricio Pochettino’s team, their fifth in succession in this fixture. The striker’s first two chances stemmed from wayward passes by Ryan Mason and Nabil Bentaleb as Tottenham’s carelessness in midfield supplied Liverpool’s attack consistently in the first half. Inevitable rustiness from Sturridge reprieved the visitors on those occasions.
 
Lazar Markovic volleyed over from close range and Lloris made an excellent save to deny Sturridge after Jordan Ibe combined with the Serb down the right. The Tottenham keeper’s next intervention was less impressive, however, as he and his defenders failed to deal with a routine clearance down the field from Simon Mignolet. Vertonghen’s unconvincing challenge on Sturridge rebounded kindly into the path of Markovic, Eric Dier dropped off for reasons best known to himself and the £20m summer signing from Benfica scuffed his shot beyond Lloris’s weak left hand and into the bottom corner.
 
Tottenham responded positively. Emre Can threw himself in the way of a Christian Eriksen shot and the Dane then combined neatly with Erik Lamela to create a 23rd goal of the season for Harry Kane. Liverpool failed to exert sufficient pressure on the Spurs’ pair outside the area, Mamadou Sakho slipped as Lamela played a disguised pass into the box and Kane was left free to drive in the equaliser between Mignolet’s legs.
 
The game continued to flow and Sturridge almost restored Liverpool’s advantage in nonchalant style when Ibe’s right-wing cross deflected into his path six yards out. The Liverpool striker was facing away from goal and surrounded by several white shirts but back-flicked the ball against the outside of a post.
 
Tottenham started the second half with purpose but it was Liverpool who regained the lead when Danny Rose was adjudged to have clipped Sturridge inside the area. Phil Dowd waved play on after the striker tumbled over the left-back’s outstretched leg only for his assistant to signal for a foul. Steven Gerrard converted the spot-kick just beyond Lloris’ finger-tips for his 10th goal of his farewell Liverpool season before being replaced with a slight hamstring problem.
 
There was further controversy when Spurs levelled for a second time. Gerrard was booked for a foul that wasn’t on Eriksen, who drew a fine save from Mignolet from the resulting free-kick, albeit with the ball dropping to Kane inside the area.
 
Kane squared – from an offside position, claimed Liverpool – and Mousa Dembélé was able to convert with his chest from close range. The offside appeals went unheeded but Balotelli, at last, would have the final word. “It was a great game and while I’m disappointed with the result, I’m also proud of the effort of our players,” said Pochettino. “We were unlucky.”


]]></TEXT>
<TAGS>
<Player id="P0" spans="169~184" text="Mario Balotelli" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P1" spans="504~513" text="Balotelli" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P2" spans="850~862" text="Adam Lallana" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P3" spans="895~909" text="Jan Vertonghen" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P4" spans="914~923" text="Balotelli" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P5" spans="953~964" text="Hugo Lloris" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P6" spans="1002~1007" text="Henry" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P7" spans="1381~1397" text="Jordan Henderson" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P8" spans="1403~1412" text="Balotelli" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P9" spans="1791~1806" text="Raheem Sterling" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P10" spans="1891~1902" text="Lucas Leiva" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P11" spans="2096~2112" text="Daniel Sturridge" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P12" spans="2184~2188" text="Hart" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P13" spans="2377~2387" text="Ryan Mason" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P14" spans="2392~2406" text="Nabil Bentaleb" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P15" spans="2533~2542" text="Sturridge" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P16" spans="2588~2602" text="Lazar Markovic" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P17" spans="2638~2644" text="Lloris" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P18" spans="2676~2685" text="Sturridge" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P19" spans="2699~2702" text="Ibe" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P20" spans="2897~2911" text="Simon Mignolet" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P21" spans="2913~2923" text="Vertonghen" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P22" spans="2952~2961" text="Sturridge" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P23" spans="2996~3004" text="Markovic" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P24" spans="3006~3015" text="Eric Dier" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P25" spans="3127~3133" text="Lloris" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P26" spans="3213~3221" text="Emre Can" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P27" spans="3252~3269" text="Christian Eriksen" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P28" spans="3319~3325" text="Lamela" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P29" spans="3366~3376" text="Harry Kane" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P30" spans="3461~3474" text="Mamadou Sakho" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P31" spans="3486~3492" text="Lamela" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P32" spans="3534~3538" text="Kane" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P33" spans="3587~3595" text="Mignolet" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P34" spans="3637~3646" text="Sturridge" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P35" spans="3710~3713" text="Ibe" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P36" spans="4013~4023" text="Danny Rose" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P37" spans="4053~4062" text="Sturridge" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P38" spans="4213~4227" text="Steven Gerrard" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P39" spans="4264~4270" text="Lloris" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P40" spans="4461~4468" text="Gerrard" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P41" spans="4506~4513" text="Eriksen" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P42" spans="4541~4549" text="Mignolet" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P43" spans="4613~4617" text="Kane" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P44" spans="4637~4641" text="Kane" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P45" spans="4708~4715" text="Dembélé" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P46" spans="4807~4816" text="Balotelli" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C0" spans="196~199" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C1" spans="447~449" text="he" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C2" spans="523~526" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C3" spans="1197~1200" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C4" spans="1249~1252" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C5" spans="1299~1301" text="he" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C6" spans="1345~1347" text="he" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C7" spans="1472~1474" text="He" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C8" spans="2126~2129" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C9" spans="2816~2818" text="he" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C10" spans="2823~2826" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C11" spans="3111~3114" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C12" spans="3748~3751" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C13" spans="4177~4180" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C14" spans="4288~4291" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C15" spans="4305~4308" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C16" spans="4741~4744" text="his" playerID="null" />
</TAGS>
</SoccEval1.1>