<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<SoccEval1.2>
<TEXT><![CDATA[http://www.theguardian.com/football/blog/2015/may/25/premier-league-2014-15-pundit-of-season

Premier League 2014-15 review: pundit of the season | Barry Glendenning


Welcome to theguardian.com review of the 2014-15 Premier League season. Now that the campaign has ended we would like you to help us choose your favourite goal, the best referee and the best manager, and other winners in a total of 10 categories.
 
We have nominated some contenders, but this is just to get the discussion going: we would like your suggestions so that we can compile the best into final polls that you can vote on. The polls will be published at midday on Tuesday 26 May, so please tell us what you think. Thanks
 Gary Neville  
In the interests of variety, some excellent pundits have been left off this end-of-season list for no other reason than that they’ve appeared in recent years and it’s time to nudge a few others worthy of praise into the spotlight. Gary Neville, however, has been a staple on this shortlist since beginning his work with Sky Sports News in 2011 and it would be a gross dereliction of journalistic duty to omit him from any attempt to drum up discussion about the current state of football punditry. You may not always agree with him but what he has to say is invariably worth hearing and his influence on the incredibly serious business of People Talking About Football has been enormous.
 
While there is little point in reiterating his capabilities in the gantry or studio, his work behind the scenes is worthy of attention. It is here that he lays the foundations, obsessing over the content of Monday Night Football with his Sky cohorts Jamie Carragher and Ed Chamberlin via text message for up to 48 hours, before arriving at the studio at 9am on Monday mornings to cajole, nit-pick, boss and make demands of his on and off air colleagues until their business concludes 14 hours later. Funny, self-deprecating but an often stroppy control freak who obsesses over every single aspect of the production process, Neville recently admitted that “goals don’t interest me”. What’s not to love?
 Richie Sadlier 
This good-humoured former Millwall striker and Republic of Ireland one-cap wonder has forged a far more remarkable career as a pundit than he ever did as a player whose career was ended at the age of 23 by a recurring hip injury. In his work as an RTE Champions League pundit, Sunday newspaper columnist and regular contributor to the excellent Second Captains podcast and its TV spin-off, the 36-year-old Dubliner is happy to draw from his own often harrowing experiences as a player prone to bouts of depression and constant doubts about his own ability. Cruelly, he was forced into retirement just as he was establishing himself as a favourite with Den regulars who had hitherto abused him relentlessly.
 
An erudite and often confrontational addition to the long established hierarchy of RTE punditry that is John Giles, Eamon Dunphy and Liam Brady, Sadlier is happy to tackle football’s many taboos but can also be very funny indeed. His tale of how Republic of Ireland youth team players used to amuse and abuse themselves against the clock to while away hours of tedium at international tournaments is 24 carat podcast gold, while his poignant meditation on the ultimately futile battle of his beloved victorian bulldog, Frank, against epilepsy, constipation and the unstoppable march of time has become the stuff of Irish broadcasting legend.
 Paul Scholes  
Considering how publicly reticent he was as a player, the level of ubiquity achieved by Paul Scholes since becoming a pundit has been surprising, but welcome. A match analyst with BT Sport and columnist with The Independent who may also be available for children’s parties, the Manchester United midfield maestro’s dry wit and low tolerance for platitudinal BS first came to public attention in Ben and Gabe Turner’s documentary The Class of ‘92. His forthright, incisive and often amusing views tend to be as accurate as those fabled long balls with which he used to pick out team-mates on the training ground, often when they’d been caught short during and were relieving themselves in faraway bushes. The Scholes of yore would almost certainly have bristled at the prospect of “going viral” but one suspects Scholes 2.0 allowed himself a chuckle for achieving exactly that upon being caught on camera calling BT’s Matchday Live co-host Robbie Savage a “knobhead”.
 Pat Nevin  
“I have purely one thought in mind when I do punditry,” said Scottish football’s answer to the Italian renaissance in an interview with the Guardian last month. “I’m gonna try and tell you something you might not know. That’s it: full stop. Underline.” A thoroughly fascinating man with a range of interests outside football that is as well documented as it is wide, Nevin seems to operate on the less lucrative fringes of the punditry world in a state of affairs that seems in keeping with his status as free spirit and indie outsider.
 
Whether it is by accident or design remains unclear, as the former Chelsea, Everton and Tranmere winger brings plenty to any party to which he is invited: his painstakingly meticulous and well researched Football Insight features on the BBC website are easily the equal of anything presented by Gary Neville and Jamie Carragher on Sky’s comparatively big budget equivalent Monday Night Football.
 Kevin Davies  
With his playing career approaching its end, the Preston North End target man has been quietly making a name for himself on BT Sport as a co-commentator for the station’s German football coverage and quite clearly arrives with his homework done, which is more than can be said of many of his peers elsewhere. Along with Danny Higginbotham, Davies is one of many small but essential cogs in the big wheel that drives the station’s terrific European football coverage. BT’s liberal mix of old pros and assorted experts from the field of journalism could make their coverage of the Champions League a delight for football nerds everywhere.
 
• Check out the other categories:
 
Match of the season
 
Signing of the season
 
Manager of the season
 
Innovations for the future
 
Player of the season
 
Flop of the season
 
Gripe of the season
 
Referee of the season


]]></TEXT>
<TAGS>
<Player id="P0" spans="148~153" text="Barry" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P1" spans="2182~2189" text="Ireland" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P2" spans="2970~2975" text="Brady" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P3" spans="3090~3097" text="Ireland" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P4" spans="5412~5418" text="Davies" playerID="null" />
<Player id="P5" spans="5761~5767" text="Davies" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C0" spans="1020~1023" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C1" spans="1255~1257" text="he" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C2" spans="1301~1304" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C3" spans="1447~1450" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C4" spans="1489~1492" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C5" spans="1556~1558" text="he" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C6" spans="1638~1641" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C7" spans="1827~1830" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C8" spans="2262~2264" text="he" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C9" spans="2356~2359" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C10" spans="2560~2563" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C11" spans="2663~2666" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C12" spans="2689~2691" text="he" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C13" spans="2727~2729" text="he" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C14" spans="3062~3065" text="His" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C15" spans="3261~3264" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C16" spans="3320~3323" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C17" spans="3524~3526" text="he" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C18" spans="3937~3940" text="His" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C19" spans="4047~4049" text="he" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C20" spans="4961~4964" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C21" spans="5149~5151" text="he" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C22" spans="5164~5167" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C23" spans="5426~5429" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C24" spans="5648~5651" text="his" playerID="null" />
<Coref id="C25" spans="5709~5712" text="his" playerID="null" />
</TAGS>
</SoccEval1.2>